(Sheldon:)I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)But in what universe
is Wonder Woman blonde?
(Howard:)Relax. No one's going to
be looking at her hair.
(Howard:)Ow!
(Howard:)I mean,
(Zack:)ow.
(Zack:)Hold on. The costume came
(Zack:)with a black wig.
Where is it, babe?
(Penny:)No. I'm not wearing
it. It looks stupid.
(Zack:)Come on. We're trying
to win a contest here.
(Penny:)Forget it. I'm not
wearing the wig.
Honey, there's no "I"
in "Justice League."
(Howard:)Well, actually...
(Leonard:)Don't.
He's making our case.
(Zack:)Okay, babe. Uh...
(Zack:)Kind of embarrassing me
in front of my friends.
(Penny:)Okay.
You know what?
(Penny:)I changed my mind.
I'm not going.
(Raj:)Looks like someone
else is going
(Raj:)to have to be Wonder Woman.
(Zack:)Babe, open up.